8tube.xxx 2017-12-10

# Privacy Policy - 8tube.xxx

**Lilly Devine SA needs to collect, obtain, use, and share certain information about You. This Privacy Policy briefly explains what We collect, who We share it with, and how You can contact 8tube.xxx in order to ensure the accuracy of the data We collect, obtain, use, and share.  
Keep in mind that the information Lilly Devine SA collects from You helps us better serve You.**

## Protection of Your privacy:

Lilly Devine SA will release data when we believe the release is appropriate to comply with the law, or to enforce our Terms & Conditions.

## Storage Of Personal Information:

Lilly Devine SA employs the latest and best techniques available for protecting its systems from intrusion by unauthorized individuals, and is constantly upgrading its security as better methods become available. All information is stored behind firewalls and other sophisticated security systems. Our data center utilizes state-of-the-art physical security measures to prevent unauthorized access to the facility.  
Lilly Devine SA does not request, or knowingly collect identifiable information from children un-der the age of 18. Lilly Devine SA does not knowingly use or share personal information from us-ers under the age of 18 with Third-Parties. Lilly Devine SA does not offer children any promotions involving games, prizes, or any other activity that would induce a child to divulge personal information.  
This Privacy Policy was posted On November 05th 2014. Lilly Devine SA reserves the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Lilly Devine SA takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. We will occasionally update our Privacy Policy and We will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review Our Privacy Policy updates

## Your Rights

You have every right to require from Us not to process and / or disclose Your personal information for marketing and commercial purposes. If, and when We plan and intend to process Your Person-al Data for commercial purposes, We will let You know.  
Furthermore, You can require this right at any time by contacting Us directly at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## Access to Information

In accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998 (˝the Act˝) You are entitled to access any in-formation We hold about You if You have registered.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Last update: November 05th 2014  
Any future changes We make to this Privacy Policy and the way We use cookies at the Website will be posted on this Website(s). We recommend that You frequently check this page to ensure You are informed and familiar with the latest version of Our Privacy Policy.

## Questions

Questions regarding the information Lilly Devine SA has stored about You should be in writing, for address details go to our contact page, or send us an email: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4b3b39223d2a28320b27222727322f66382a65282426).
